一旦你学习了怎样解析 JSON 数据，那么就非常
Once you've learned how to pars JSON data, it's pretty
直观地能够解析余下
straight forward to be able to pars the rest of the
我们需要的字段。因为这并不是一个Java或JSON的课程，
fields that we need. Since this isn't a course on
我们将在下面的gist中提供解析的代码。
Java or JSON, we're going to provide you with the parsing
这就是gist的样子。
code in the gist below. And this is what the
共有三个辅助方法。第一个是
gist looks like. There are three helper methods. The first is
格式化日期。第二个是四舍五入温度。第三个是
for formatting dates. The second is for rounding temperatures. The third
将forecastJsonStr转化成天气预测的数组。
is for turning a forecastJsonStr, into an array of weather forecasts.
更新FetchWeatherTask使用这些辅助方法。并且
Update the Fetch Weather Tasks to use these helpful functions. And
在doinbackground方法中应该返回一个预测的字符串数组。
the do in background method should return a string array of
你能够输出日志去检查数组是不是
forecasts. You can log the output to check that the array
正确。一天的预测的格式应该看起来像这样。
is correct. The format of one day's forecast should look like this.